// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single

export const quiz = {
  totalQuestions: 15,
  perQuestionScore: 10,
  questions: [
      {
          question: 'What is the name of Aang\'s flying bison?',
          choices: ['Appa', 'Momo', 'Naga', 'Fang'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Appa',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the main character\'s name in the series?',
          choices: ['Zuko', 'Katara', 'Sokka', 'Aang'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Aang',
      },
      {
          question: 'Who is the Avatar before Aang?',
          choices: ['Korra', 'Kyoshi', 'Roku', 'Yangchen'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Roku',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is Toph Beifong\'s nickname?',
          choices: ['The Boulder', 'The Blind Bandit', 'The Earth King', 'The Fire Lord'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'The Blind Bandit',
      },
      {
          question: 'What type of bender is Katara?',
          choices: ['Waterbender', 'Firebender', 'Earthbender', 'Airbender'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Waterbender',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is Sokka\'s weapon of choice?',
          choices: ['Sword', 'Boomerang', 'Spear', 'Club'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Boomerang',
      },
      {
          question: 'Who is the leader of the Fire Nation?',
          choices: ['Ozai', 'Azula', 'Zuko', 'Iroh'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Ozai',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the name of Zuko\'s sister?',
          choices: ['Ty Lee', 'Mai', 'Azula', 'Suki'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Azula',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the name of Aang\'s mentor and friend, who runs a tea shop?',
          choices: ['Bumi', 'Iroh', 'Jeong Jeong', 'Pakku'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Iroh',
      },
      {
          question: 'Who is known as "The Painted Lady"?',
          choices: ['Suki', 'Mai', 'Ty Lee', 'Katara'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Katara',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the name of the group Aang and his friends form to fight the Fire Nation?',
          choices: ['Team Avatar', 'Firebenders United', 'The Phoenix Squad', 'The Freedom Fighters'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Team Avatar',
      },
      {
          question: 'Who is the leader of the Kyoshi Warriors?',
          choices: ['Suki', 'Toph', 'Katara', 'Mai'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Suki',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the name of the library hidden in the desert?',
          choices: ['The Spirit Library', 'The Ancient Archives', 'The Wan Shi Tong Library', 'The Forbidden Library'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'The Wan Shi Tong Library',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the name of the city that is home to the Earth King?',
          choices: ['Ba Sing Se', 'Omashu', 'Kyoshi Island', 'Yu Dao'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Ba Sing Se',
      },
      {
          question: 'What is the highest level of earthbending mastery in the series?',
          choices: ['Earth Sage', 'Earth King', 'Earth Avatar', 'Metalbending'],
          type: 'MCQs',
          correctAnswer: 'Metalbending',
      },
  ],
};
